Candy, chicks and rock 'n' roll.
Hop is a animation, comedy, family film directed by Tim Hill.
E.B., the Easter Bunny's teenage son, heads to Hollywood,
determined to become a drummer in a rock 'n' roll band.
In L.A., he's taken in by Fred after the out-of-work slacker hits E.B.
with his car.
E.B (voice), played by Russell Brand.
Fred, played by James Marsden.
Samantha O'Hare, played by Kaley Cuoco.
Carlos / Phil (voice), played by Hank Azaria.
Bonnie O'Hare, played by Elizabeth Perkins.
Henry O'Hare, played by Gary Cole.
Hop is a 2011 American live-action animated Easter comedy film directed by Tim
Hill and written by Brian Lynch, Cinco Paul, and Ken Daurio.
Produced by Illumination Entertainment, it stars James Marsden, Kaley Cuoco, Gary Cole, Elizabeth Perkins, David
Hasselhoff, and Chelsea Handler, with the voices of Russell Brand, Hank Azaria, and Hugh Laurie.
The film follows a young rabbit who would rather drum in a band than succeed his
father as the Easter Bunny, and befriends a human slacker seeking a job.
Hop premiered at Universal Studios Hollywood on March 27, 2011, and was theatrically released in the
United States on April 1 by Universal Pictures, and received mixed reviews from critics.
It was a box-office success, grossing $188.5
million against a budget of $63 million.
The film explores themes of bunny, coup d'etat, villain, slacker, easter.
The tone is lighthearted.